igigi.com 2019-10-23

# Privacy Policies

#### Privacy Statement for igigi.com    **This policy was last updated  April 15, 2019.**

#### IGIGI has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for www.igigi.com 

PRIVACY STATEMENT

\----

This Web site (this "Site") is operated by IGIGI, Inc. We recognize that privacy is a major concern for our customers (“customers”) and we respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy is to advise you how we will and will not disclose the information provided to us through this Site. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, contact us at Customer Service. If elements of our Privacy Policy change, we will post them here. This Privacy Policy applies to all information obtained through this Site.

SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?

We collect information online when you register with us. This information includes your name, e-mail address, mailing address, and may include your phone number. We also may ask you for your mailing preferences should you choose to join our mailing list and if you would like to participate in consumer research. When we conduct sales, we will also collect information necessary to complete the sale and process your order such as shipping address, credit card numbers (and expiration dates) and related information.

When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

IGIGI collects information from you to fulfill your orders and requests, and to communicate with you about our company, our affiliates and our products. In addition, we may use information about your product interests and purchases to help us improve our Site design and your online experience.

We may combine information you provide with demographic information that is available from other sources. We use this combined information to enhance and personalize your online experience with us, and to communicate more effectively with you by e-mail or otherwise. We will not share your information with anyone outside of IGIGI.

Email marketing: With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

SECTION 2 - CONSENT

How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

How do I withdraw my consent?

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at service@IGIGI.com or mailing us at:

IGIGI/Mylinego, Inc , Online Consent, 1900 South Norfolk Street, Suite 350   
San Mateo, CA 94403 United States

SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE

IGIGI will not disclose any collected information with any and all unrelated third parties for the sake of commercial gain. In the event that IGIGI's or any of our affiliates' or subsidiaries' businesses or assets are sold, customer information will be one of the transferred assets. We may share customer information with law enforcement agencies in the event of a criminal investigation or suspected illegal activity with or without requiring a court order or a subpoena.

SECTION 4 - SHOPIFY

Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.

Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

Payment:

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service (https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms) or Privacy Statement (https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).

SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

Links

The Site contains links to other sites that are not under our control nor covered by IGIGI's policies regarding privacy. We have no control of or responsibility for linked Web sites and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. You should check the privacy policies, if any, of these linked sites to see how they may use your personal information. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

Google analytics:

Our store uses Google Analytics to help us learn about who visits our site and what pages are being looked at.

SECTION 6 - SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption.  Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

SECTION 7 - COOKIES

A cookie is a small alphanumeric data file that Web sites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit their sites. Cookies identify a unique anonymous visitor’s browser. They do not retrieve personal data from your hard drive or obtain any information about who you are. We do not identify a visitor unless they have chosen to register on our Site. We use the information gathered through cookies to recognize a returning registered visitor for the purpose of activating personalized features and settings. We also use cookies to recognize visitor traffic patterns and Site usage on an aggregate and anonymous basis to improve the Site’s layout and design.

 Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.

 _session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).

 _shopify_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits

 _shopify_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.

cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.

 _secure_session_id, unique token, sessional

 storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

 PREF, persistent for a very short period, Set by Google and tracks who visits the store and from where

SECTION 8 - AGE OF CONSENT

Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, IGIGI will not knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that a subscriber is under the age of 13 and has registered without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable registration information from our files.

SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at brad@IGIGI.com or by mail at

IGIGI

[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]

IGIGI/Mylinego, Inc , Online Consent,  1900 South Norfolk Street,  Suite 350   
San Mateo, CA 94403  United States
